Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ولكنني لا أزال غير قادر على العثور على أي أثر لك♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪مثل حوت يغرق في شقوق البحر العميق♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، وأفقد نفسي تمامًا♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
♪بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك♪
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
♪أصرخ وأنا أسقط في الهاوية المظلمة♪
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪العودة إلى الوراء ليست سوى موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪المبالغة في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
What
ماذا
are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sneaking into my room
التسلل إلى غرفتي
in the dead of night,
في منتصف الليل،
looking for death
البحث عن الموت
or me?
أو أنا؟
If you truly wanted me dead,
إذا كنت تريدني حقا ميتا،
when I accidentally took opium yesterday,
عندما تناولت الأفيون بالخطأ أمس،
why bother saving me with a kiss?
لماذا تهتم بإنقاذي بقبلة؟
Or is it
أم أنه
you're afraid if I die,
أنت خائف إذا مت،
you'll lose your scapegoat?
هل ستخسر كبش الفداء الخاص بك؟
You think a single kiss is enough to soften me?
هل تعتقد أن قبلة واحدة كافية لتليينني؟
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
those tricks you learned at Huaying Brothel
تلك الحيل التي تعلمتها في بيت الدعارة هواينغ
are...
نكون...
Useless against you?
عديم الفائدة ضدك؟
You talk tough, Mr. Lin,
أنت تتحدث بقوة، السيد لين،
but you're secretly investigating behind Song Zhichu's back.
لكنك تقوم بالتحقيق سراً خلف ظهر سونغ تشيتشو.
Aren't you afraid he'll find out?
ألا تخافين من أن يكتشف الأمر؟
Are you threatening me?
هل تهددني؟
It's not a threat.
إنه ليس تهديدا.
You and I,
أنت وأنا،
husband and wife, working as one.
زوج وزوجة يعملان كشخص واحد.
We can cut through any challenges.
نحن قادرون على التغلب على أي تحديات.
Lu Man is coming tomorrow.
لو مان قادم غدا.
Work with me and put on a show.
اعمل معي وقدم عرضًا.
Xu Yin, this invitation of yours is quite elegant.
شو يين، هذه الدعوة الخاصة بك أنيقة للغاية.
But I do wonder,
ولكنني أتساءل،
what kind of ensnaring banquet you're hosting today?
ما هو نوع المأدبة المذهلة التي تستضيفها اليوم؟
Liang Yi, stop teasing me.
ليانغ يي، توقف عن مضايقتي.
During those days we spent together,
خلال تلك الأيام التي قضيناها معًا،
I was just young and impulsive.
لقد كنت صغيراً ومتسرعاً.
But after what happened at the Dai family yesterday,
ولكن بعد ما حدث في عائلة داي أمس،
I finally saw for myself
لقد رأيت ذلك بنفسي أخيرا
how vicious society ladies can be.
كم يمكن أن تكون سيدات المجتمع شرسات.
After thinking it over,
بعد التفكير في الأمر،
out of all the noblewomen in Rong City,
من بين جميع النساء النبيلات في مدينة رونغ،
you're the only one who's genuine
أنت الوحيد الحقيقي
and worth befriending.
وتستحق الصداقة.
You're now the head lady of the Chengyun Society.
أنت الآن رئيسة جمعية تشنغيون.
Why bother trying to form any sisterhood at all?
لماذا تهتم بمحاولة تشكيل أي أخوة على الإطلاق؟
Oh, you don't know the half of it.
أوه، أنت لا تعرف نصف الأمر.
My marriage might as well not exist.
ربما لا يكون زواجي موجودًا.
I spend every day alone in an empty room,
أقضي كل يوم وحدي في غرفة فارغة،
and I can't tell if my husband is busy or just pretending to be.
ولا أستطيع أن أحدد إذا كان زوجي مشغولاً أم يتظاهر بذلك فقط.
You mean...
هل تقصد...
Lin Yun hasn't shared a room with you?
هل لم يشارك لين يون الغرفة معك؟
I have no one to complain to.
ليس لدي أحد أشتكي إليه.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
I keep feeling
أنا أستمر في الشعور
there's someone else in his heart.
هناك شخص آخر في قلبه
Have you ever heard
هل سبق لك أن سمعت
any rumors about him and another woman?
هل هناك شائعات عنه وعن امرأة أخرى؟
How would I know that?
كيف يمكنني أن أعرف ذلك؟
However,
لكن،
your husband certainly draws attention.
من المؤكد أن زوجك يلفت الانتباه.
Whether you can keep an eye on him is up to you.
إن كان بإمكانك مراقبته أم لا، فهذا الأمر متروك لك.
Keep an eye on him? How?
راقبه؟ كيف؟
I'm an orphan girl.
أنا فتاة يتيمة.
I can't help him with anything.
لا أستطيع مساعدته في أي شيء.
But Lin Yun often tells me
لكن لين يون يخبرني في كثير من الأحيان
that you're not only beautiful,
أنك لست جميلة فقط،
but come from a wealthy family,
ولكنهم يأتون من عائلة ثرية،
and now you've become head of the Liang family,
والآن أصبحت رئيسًا لعائلة ليانغ،
managing the Liang family business.
إدارة أعمال عائلة ليانغ.
Both in life and in business, you're a huge help to Chief Song.
في كل من الحياة والعمل، أنت مساعدة كبيرة للرئيس سونغ.
You're the kind of wife people rarely find.
أنت نوع الزوجة التي نادرًا ما يجدها الناس.
He really said that?
هل قال ذلك حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
As for me,
أما بالنسبة لي،
I'd be lucky to match even half of you.
سأكون محظوظًا إذا تمكنت من مطابقة نصفكم.
Isn't that Mr. Lin's car?
أليست هذه سيارة السيد لين؟
Since I'm visiting today,
بما أنني أزوركم اليوم،
I should at least
ينبغي لي على الأقل
go greet him properly.
اذهب وسلم عليه بشكل لائق.
I get terribly bored at the Chengyun Society.
أشعر بالملل الشديد في جمعية تشنغيون.
Those boys
هؤلاء الأولاد
call me "Sister-in-law", sure,
نادني "أخت الزوج" بالتأكيد،
but everyone knows in their hearts
لكن الجميع يعلمون في قلوبهم
I'm only the daughter of the man who saved Lin Yun.
أنا فقط ابنة الرجل الذي أنقذ لين يون.
Liang Yi, if you're willing,
ليانغ يي، إذا كنت على استعداد،
come visit me more often.
تعالوا لزيارتي أكثر.
We can talk and keep each other company.
يمكننا التحدث ونبقى مع بعضنا البعض.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Just don't find me annoying later.
فقط لا تجدني مزعجًا لاحقًا.
How could I?
كيف يمكنني ذلك؟
I'd be thrilled if you came.
سوف أكون سعيدًا إذا أتيت.
It was here just now.
لقد كان هنا للتو.
Madam Li.
Madam Li.
Fetch Mr. Lin.
احضر السيد لين.
Yes.
نعم.
Mr. Lin looks like someone who kills without blinking,
السيد لين يبدو وكأنه شخص يقتل دون أن يرمش،
yet his room is decorated so tastefully.
ومع ذلك فإن غرفته مزينة بذوق رفيع.
Right?
يمين؟
He's no longer the street hooligan
لم يعد هو المشاغب في الشارع
who used to trail behind my father.
الذي كان يتبع والدي.
No wonder he looks down on me now.
لا عجب أنه ينظر إلي الآن.
Madam Song.
السيدة سونغ.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
An earring.
قرط.
I can see it's an earring.
أستطيع أن أرى أنها قرط.
I'm asking whose it is.
أنا أسأل من هو؟
Isn't it yours?
أليس هذا لك؟
It's not mine.
إنها ليست لي.
I don't own anything like this.
لا أملك شيئا مثل هذا.
All this time we've been married, have you ever bought me real jewelry?
لقد تزوجنا طوال هذه المدة، هل اشتريت لي مجوهرات حقيقية؟
It's all cheap gold-plated rubbish.
إنها كلها مجرد هراء مطلي بالذهب الرخيص.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Which stray woman does this belong to?
لأي امرأة ضالة تنتمي هذه؟
You even kept it on you
حتى أنك احتفظت به عليك
so you can think about her, right?
حتى تتمكن من التفكير بها، أليس كذلك؟
When we married, you promised
عندما تزوجنا، وعدت
you'd only ever have me.
لن يكون لديك سوى أنا.
Now you want the company of wives?
الآن تريد صحبة الزوجات؟
If you don't want this marriage, just say so.
إذا كنت لا تريد هذا الزواج، فقط قل ذلك.
Instead, you keep me at home as decoration
بدلا من ذلك، يمكنك الاحتفاظ بي في المنزل كديكور.
while you sneak around with some tramp.
بينما تتسلل مع بعض المتشردين.
Lin Yun,
لين يون,
is this how you repay my late father?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تكافئ بها والدي الراحل؟
Enough.
كافٍ.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
you tell me if I'm wrong.
أخبرني إذا كنت مخطئا.
If he doesn't hand over that woman today,
إذا لم يسلم تلك المرأة اليوم،
I...
أنا...
I'll hang myself at the Chengyun Society gates!
سأشنق نفسي على أبواب جمعية تشنغيون!
Xu Yin.
شو يين.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Calm down? How?
هدئ من روعك؟ كيف؟
Tell me, how am I supposed to live like this?
أخبرني كيف من المفترض أن أعيش هكذا؟
Maybe
ربما
this is a misunderstanding.
هذا سوء فهم.
Look.
ينظر.
Let me ask him.
دعني أسأله.
Madam Li,
Madam Li,
take Madam downstairs.
خذ السيدة إلى الطابق السفلي.
Liang Yi, you have to speak up for me.
ليانغ يي، عليك أن تتحدث نيابة عني.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Lin Yun, you scoudrel!
لين يون، أيها الوغد!
You're heartless!
أنت بلا قلب!
What
ماذا
are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I lost one of my earrings yesterday.
لقد فقدت أحد الأقراط الخاصة بي أمس.
Never thought I'd find it here with you, Mr. Lin.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن أجدها هنا معك، السيد لين.
So, it belongs to you.
لذا، فهو ملك لك.
You helped me again yesterday.
لقد ساعدتني مرة أخرى بالأمس.
My wife was the one who helped you.
زوجتي هي التي ساعدتك.
Today, I finally get to see
اليوم، أستطيع أن أرى أخيرا
just how loving you two are.
كم أنتم محبون لبعضكم البعض.
Lin Yun.
لين يون.
Appearances are for outsiders.
المظاهر للغرباء.
Only you know
أنت فقط من يعرف
where your heart really is.
حيث يوجد قلبك حقا.
Why bother pretending otherwise?
لماذا نتظاهر بخلاف ذلك؟
You're the great Miss Liang.
أنت السيدة العظيمة ليانغ.
Is sleeping around
ينام حول
all you know what to do?
كل ما تعرفه هو ماذا تفعل؟
Blame yourself for being too charming.
ألقي اللوم على نفسك لكونك ساحرًا جدًا.
No wonder Lu Man is obsessed with you.
لا عجب أن لو مان مهووس بك.
If we're talking about sleeping around,
إذا كنا نتحدث عن النوم حول،
I'm nothing compared to you and Song Zhichu.
أنا لا شيء مقارنة بك وبـ سونغ تشيتشو.
Don't you remember
ألا تتذكر؟
whose bed I woke up in?
في أي سرير استيقظت؟
The whole city knows you're my wife now.
الآن عرفت المدينة كلها أنك زوجتي.
And you still pushed your own husband into another woman's arms.
ومازلت تدفعين زوجك إلى أحضان امرأة أخرى.
You think that's appropriate?
هل تعتقد أن هذا مناسب؟
I'm only your wife in name.
أنا زوجتك بالإسم فقط.
Did you forget?
هل نسيت؟
Funny, you mention that.
مضحك أنك ذكرت ذلك.
You're actually Madam Song.
أنت في الواقع السيدة سونغ.
You and Song Zhichu grew up together.
لقد نشأت أنت وسونغ تشيتشو معًا.
Childhood sweethearts.
أحباء الطفولة.
Practically destined to marry.
من المقرر عمليا أن يتزوج.
So wouldn't seducing Song Zhichu
لذا لن يكون من الجيد إغواء سونغ تشيتشو
make a lot more sense?
هل هذا يجعل الأمر أكثر منطقية؟
Xu Yin.
شو يين.
Did you ask him for me?
هل سألته لي؟
Which woman has he been messing with?
مع أية امرأة كان يتلاعب؟
Xu Yin,
شو يين,
listen to me.
استمع لي.
Men
الرجال
are always going to stray.
سوف تضل الطريق دائمًا.
Turn a blind eye,
غض الطرف
and life gets a lot easier.
وتصبح الحياة أسهل كثيرًا.
Ling Yi, tell me.
لينغ يي، أخبرني.
Am I really that bad at satisfying him?
هل أنا حقا سيئة في إرضائه؟
Is that why he's messing around outside?
هل هذا هو السبب الذي يجعله يتجول في الخارج؟
He's been snapping at me for no reason these days.
لقد كان يصرخ في وجهي بدون سبب هذه الأيام.
Maybe his qi and blood are blocked.
ربما تم حظر تشي ودمه.
Why don't you take me to the Liang shop for some herbs?
لماذا لا تأخذني إلى متجر ليانغ لشراء بعض الأعشاب؟
I'll brew the medicine for him.
سأحضر له الدواء.
Maybe then he'll come back to me.
ربما سيعود إلي بعد ذلك.
A physical illness is easy to cure,
إن المرض الجسدي سهل الشفاء،
but the heart is another matter.
ولكن القلب أمر آخر.
Come with me then, Xu Yin.
تعال معي إذن، شو يين.
Thank you, Liang Yi.
شكرا لك، ليانغ يي.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Miss.
يفتقد.
What brings you?
ماذا جاء بك؟
Are you feeling unwell?
هل تشعر بتوعك؟
I'm the head of the Liang family now.
أنا رئيس عائلة ليانغ الآن.
What?
ماذا؟
I can't come unless I'm sick?
لا أستطيع الحضور إلا إذا كنت مريضًا؟
Or are you hoping I fall ill?
أم أنك تأمل أن أمرض؟
I spoke out of turn.
لقد تحدثت خارج دوري.
Please,
لو سمحت،
don't be upset.
لا تنزعج.
Since you know your mistake,
بما أنك تعرف خطأك،
I'll just dock one month's wages.
سأخصم من راتب شهر واحد فقط.
What?
ماذا؟
My word doesn't count anymore?
كلمتي لم تعد ذات قيمة؟
No, no.
لا لا.
You're absolutely right.
أنت على حق تماما.
I'll take the punishment.
سأتحمل العقوبة.
Much better.
أفضل بكثير.
Give Madam Lin a prescription for qi stagnation.
أعطي السيدة لين وصفة لعلاج ركود تشي.
Yes.
نعم.
Xu Yin, you're impressive.
شو يين، أنت مثير للإعجاب.
I heard the Liang family has a very rare specimen of coptis.
سمعت أن عائلة ليانغ لديها عينة نادرة جدًا من القبطيس.
Could I have the honor of seeing it?
هل يمكن أن يكون لي شرف رؤيته؟
Why not?
ولم لا؟
Come with me.
تعال معي.
(Liang's Apothecary)
(صيدلية ليانغ)
Miss, you can't go in there.
آنسة، لا يمكنك الدخول إلى هناك.
Move.
يتحرك.
I said move.
قلت تحرك.
Manager.
مدير.
Miss insists on entering.
تصر السيدة على الدخول.
I...
أنا...
Miss. The Young Master gave strict orders.
لقد أعطى السيد الشاب أوامر صارمة.
No one enters the warehouse but him.
لا أحد يدخل المستودع سواه.
Not even me?
ولا حتى انا؟
Young master said
قال السيد الشاب
no one must enter.
لا يجوز لأحد الدخول.
Please don't make things hard for us.
من فضلك لا تجعل الأمور صعبة علينا.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Looks like your husband is the real master of the Liang family.
يبدو أن زوجك هو السيد الحقيقي لعائلة ليانغ.
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
This is the Liang family's shop.
هذا هو متجر عائلة ليانغ.
I'm the head of the Liang family.
أنا رئيس عائلة ليانغ.
Song Zhichu is nothing but a son-in-law.
سونغ تشيتشو ليس سوى صهر.
Why should I listen to him?
لماذا يجب أن أستمع إليه؟
Miss, please don't be angry.
آنسة، من فضلك لا تغضبي.
Should I send someone to fetch the Young Master?
هل يجب أن أرسل شخصًا لإحضار السيد الشاب؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
Today, I'm taking charge myself.
اليوم، أنا أتولى المسؤولية بنفسي.
Move.
يتحرك.
Inform the Young Master. Now.
أبلغ السيد الشاب الآن.
Yes.
نعم.
Go ahead and look around.
إذهب وانظر حولك.
Thank you, Liang Yi.
شكرا لك، ليانغ يي.
I didn't expect they hid such good stuff in here.
لم أتوقع أنهم يخبئون مثل هذه الأشياء الجيدة هنا.
I should've come sooner.
كان ينبغي لي أن آتي عاجلا.
(The opium really is still in the warehouse.)
(الأفيون لا يزال موجودًا في المستودع حقًا.)
(I'll have to figure out a way to get the goods out)
(سيتعين علي أن أجد طريقة لإخراج البضائع)
(through Lu Man.)
(من خلال لو مان.)
Miss,
يفتقد،
the Young Master is here.
السيد الشاب هنا.
Zhichu.
تشيتشو.
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
It's getting late.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا.
I'll take Madam Lin home.
سوف آخذ السيدة لين إلى المنزل.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Take care.
يعتني.
Madam Lin.
Madam Lin.
There's something I've been meaning to ask you.
هناك شيء كنت أريد أن أسألك عنه.
Chief Song, go ahead.
الرئيس سونغ، اذهب للأمام.
Why
لماذا
did you purposely befriend my wife?
هل عمدا أصبحت صديقا لزوجتي؟
Chief Song, you misunderstood.
رئيس سونغ، لقد أخطأت الفهم.
Madam Song and I hit it off right away.
لقد نجحنا أنا والسيدة سونغ في التواصل على الفور.
The day Ruyi died, what did she say to you?
يوم ماتت رويي ماذا قالت لك؟
Just nonsense a desperate woman blurts out.
مجرد هراء تقوله امرأة يائسة.
I didn't take it to heart.
لم آخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
Drop the act.
أسقط الفعل.
At the banquet, you pushed Liang Yi onstage to embarrass her.
في المأدبة، قمت بدفع ليانغ يي إلى المسرح لإحراجها.
And today, you pulled off another scheme.
واليوم نجحت في تنفيذ خطة أخرى.
I really did underestimate you.
لقد قللت من شأنك حقا.
Chief Song, let's talk this out.
يا رئيس سونغ، دعنا نتحدث عن هذا الأمر.
Please take your hand off me.
من فضلك ارفع يدك عني.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Weren't you from Huaying Brothel?
ألم تكن من بيت الدعارة هواينغ؟
Married Lin Yun for a few days and already forgot your roots?
تزوجت لين يون لبضعة أيام ونسيت جذورك بالفعل؟
Chief Song,
رئيس سونغ،
show some respect.
أظهر بعض الاحترام.
I am Lin Yun's wife.
أنا زوجة لين يون.
Great.
عظيم.
Let's see if Lin Yun is really willing to turn against me for a woman like you.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان لين يون على استعداد حقًا للانقلاب ضدي من أجل امرأة مثلك.
Let go.
اتركه.
Cursed woman!
امرأة ملعونة!
I'm taking you home.
سأأخذك إلى المنزل.
♪When we first met, we just nodded politely♪
♪عندما التقينا لأول مرة، أومأنا برؤوسنا بأدب♪
♪I never thought I'd get to hold your hand♪
♪لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن أتمكن من إمساك يدك♪
♪Leaning on each other in the cold wind♪
♪الاعتماد على بعضنا البعض في الرياح الباردة♪
♪Walking together for so long♪
♪المشي معًا لفترة طويلة♪
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفع الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأ أدائك المتكلف♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪المقامر الأكثر حماقة♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪أعامل الحب كفريسة، لا أهتم بأي شيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
♪تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء واضحة في ذهني♪
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪هذه هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪النصر يتكشف بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪استدعاء الستار♪